Jessica Wise

SUMMARY

Experienced Customer Success Advocate with 4+ years of experience improving customer experiences, looking to further develop my career in UX Design and UX Development . Previously responsible for nurturing client relationships, ensuring client happiness, retention and concerns with templated Real Estate web solutions. Assisted clients with editing the templated solution with custom CSS and JS to better fit personal branding and web site needs. Experience working closely with sales, renewals, marketing and product teams to ensure client feedback is used to make data driven decisions and improvements to the product. Outgoing self-starter with a passion to learn and grow in any setting.

Looking to help companies grow and evolve their products to meet internal and external client needs and expectations. Keenly interested in innovation-driven startups looking to make a footprint in the tech community.

EXPERIENCE

StreetSmarts, Remote — *Part Time UX Designer*

APR 2018 - PRESENT

- Handle the UX Design process from start to finish for all features and redesigns
- Conduct all user research via the facebook group or user interviews
- Design mid to high fidelity wireframes and Invision prototypes
- Create technical documentation for wireframes to be handed off to engineers
- Participate in sprint planning sessions

Placester, Inc., **Boston**, **MA** — Support UX Engineer

JAN 2018 - MAR 2018

- Managed onboardings and client happiness for a Book of Business that consisted of Real Estate Agents and Brokers of varying technical background
- Exceeded client expectations by providing HTML and CSS skills along with JS knowledge to better customize the templated solution to match clients' personal branding and website needs
- Assisted with internal testing of CSS and JS changes made to templates
- Assisted clients and coworkers with editing of logos and pictures to better fit within the templated websites
- Understood client needs and expectations and achieved a 5 star CSAT survey rating for all months employed

Rogue Wave Software, Boston, MA — Customer Success Advocate

JAN 2017 - JAN 2018

- Worked with the sales team and clients directly to understand what the client's short and long-term goals were, and how we could utilize our onboardings, webinars and tech calls to support them in achieving those goals
- Tasked to spearhead the research to reduce customer churn rate
- Conducted extensive client research in regard to license operations
- Supported the company in a full redesign of the license operations strategy
- Provided Sales, Renewals and Marketing teams with technical expertise on our entire suite of products and the capabilities that could be beneficial to the client's needs at hand
- Managed 1000+ client accounts with 6 to 100 end users including Verizon, TD Bank, CGI, Google and USDA

173 Main St Apt 1 Malden, MA 02148 (413) 727-5977

jessica.lee.wise@gmail.com https://jessicawise.github.io/port folio/

EDUCATION

Columbus College of Art and Design (CCAD) Bachelor of Fine Arts in Animation 2012

General Assembly UX Design 2018

HIGHLIGHTS

Customer Oriented

Creative Thinker

Problem Solver

Able to work with all teams of varying sizes

Tech-savvy

KNOWLEDGE BASE

HTML

CSS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Sketch

Invision

SCRUM/Agile

VueJS

ReactJS

Bootstrap

Salesforce.com

Desk.com

Jira